<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- DATA_FINGERPRINT:83eb3cf8cc2bc467743bb8e2f9e896da -->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Internet Society Events</title>
        <link>https://opportunities.internetsociety.org</link>
        <description>Latest events to get involved with Internet Society initiatives</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://opportunities.internetsociety.org/community-events/data/events.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
                    <title>What does Digital Sovereignty means for the Civil Society?</title>
                    <link>https://www.isoc.ch/events/public-policy-sessions-2026-what-does-digital-sovereignty-mean-for-the-civil-society/</link>
                    <description>ISOC Switzerland Chapter’s yearly Public Policy Sessions event will be dedicated in 2026 on the concept of digital sovereignty, launching a long term campaign asking the question “What does digital sovereignty mean?” from the perspective of different actors. As a US-based organization defending digital rights across the world since the 90s, the Internet Society’s European Chapters can play a key role in making sure that the current wave of European claims on digital sovereignty will strengthen digital rights worldwide, while taking into account important challenges related to ecological sustainability, health, and resilience and key values like openness, privacy, and democracy. We are proud to welcome in Zurich 5 special guests with strong expertise on this topic from an academic and/or policy perspective, and active engagement with various civil society organizations, like ISOC Germany and Serbia, FSFE, Wikimedia, La Quadrature du Net. You will have also the chance to meet the growing ISOC Switzerland Chapter and its new home at the center of Zurich, the L200 space, and participate in the discussion!</description>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:22:15 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3d738e277fa91af986db1420bcc96d1f</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Roundtable</category>
                    <category>Europe</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>Art by the Internet</title>
                    <link>https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfnaaKL33mC1CS8XtuafsC-Wr_5icnS7XDWAsdEDYkV6-_X8g/viewform?usp=publish-editor</link>
                    <description>A talk by DY Kim</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:24:54 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">880e022495f4abf38c99aa602b6c79f5</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Webinar</category>
                    <category>Asia Pacific</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>Meta-Layer Design Challenge</title>
                    <link>https://luma.com/lpml</link>
                    <description>The Meta-Layer Design Challenge is a global, week-long design challenge exploring how learning, collaboration, and collective intelligence can be supported above the existing Web through a shared civic interface layer - the Meta-Layer. Rather than building new platforms, participants are invited to design concepts, interfaces, and governance models that operate across websites using overlays, shared context, trust signals, and community coordination. The challenge emphasizes human-centered design, interoperability, and public-interest outcomes. The Design Challenge is part of Meta-Layer Week (January 21–28, 2025), co-hosted with Learning Planet. Activities include live sessions, workshops, demonstrations, office hours, and a final showcase. Participants may submit conceptual designs, mockups, diagrams, governance proposals, or lightweight prototypes. No coding is required. Both a Student Track and an Open Track are offered, with shared judging criteria focused on creativity, feasibility, and relevance to collective learning and public-interest infrastructure. The challenge is relevant to Internet governance, digital public infrastructure, education, and community-driven innovation, and aligns with long-standing Internet Society interests in an open, trustworthy, and people-centered Internet.  Audience: Students, educators, designers, technologists, researchers, and community organizers</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:19:19 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5ca06dfeb67d6a47e94d3c03a835aa8a</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Workshop</category>
                    <category>Global</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>Budding Polymath</title>
                    <link>https://forms.gle/xCjYZu6e4mNoY2ts7</link>
                    <description>An intra-chapter event which showcases our young talent presenting on relevant topics</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">92eb82a0bd0da51d62009d8afcdfb89a</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Conference</category>
                    <category>Asia Pacific</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>LINUX Para Uso Cotidiano</title>
                    <link>https://www.isoc.pr</link>
                    <description>Este seminario introduce a Linux como una herramienta útil para el uso cotidiano. Se presentará el trasfondo operativo del sistema, las diferencias entre diversas distribuciones y cómo obtenerlas e instalarlas en distintas plataformas. Incluye demostraciones prácticas del entorno Linux y una sesión interactiva de preguntas y respuestas para aclarar dudas y guiar a quienes deseen comenzar a utilizar este sistema operativo en su vida diaria.</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:28:49 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8ee9bf5e4deba0dc26624ef3cf716abf</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Webinar</category>
                    <category>Latin America &amp; Caribbean</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>AI SIG &quot;Wire-Free Sewer Vision&quot; Hybrid Hackathon</title>
                    <link>https://www.ai-workshops.org/</link>
                    <description>A critical event designed to challenge how we monitor and maintain underground sewer systems using cutting-edge, autonomous technology.</description>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:34:50 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2b326f3831b144526df9daed87043ddc</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Workshop</category>
                    <category>Global</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>Universal Acceptance on a Multilingual Internet</title>
                    <link>https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1YRma6AO9meGW28bn0wHIyrhJjmy87IzML7DVtUsuc68/edit?chromeless=1</link>
                    <description>This webinar will explore how Universal Acceptance forms the foundation for a truly multilingual Internet, the challenges of regional language support, multilingual DNS, inclusion in digital platforms, and the transformative role of technology, design, and policy in shaping linguistic equity online.</description>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 04:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">1859f5db4e1d46ce81a034d29981a35a</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Webinar</category>
                    <category>Asia Pacific</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>ISOC PT 2025 Internet Research Prize</title>
                    <link>https://isoc.pt/entrega-do-premio-2025/</link>
                    <description>Delivery of the ISOC PT 2025 Internet Research Prize and panel discussion on the Age Control proposals</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:08:43 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">a6f9988c15da2fce0164d2edefde1c3f</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Conference</category>
                    <category>Europe</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>UK Internet Governance Forum 2025</title>
                    <link>https://ukigf.org.uk/events/uk-igf-2025/</link>
                    <description>One-day event in London focused on “Building Digital Governance Together,” exploring key issues like digital cooperation, trust, innovation, and universal digital rights to shape the future of internet governance in the UK</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">22f88d518570f9b2928f7642f2aa16c5</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Conference</category>
                    <category>Europe</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>How to Find Funders and Partners</title>
                    <link>https://us02web.zoom.us/j/86205975631?pwd=tcfdRf3B0pPGwNCQW8RTsaazSWYUy3.1</link>
                    <description>Webinar organized by Ghana chapter to educate others on how to find funders and partners for their activities.</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:37:25 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e74ca46c8497afd832db76dd52c2815f</guid>
                    <category>Event</category>
                    <category>Webinar</category>
                    <category>Africa</category>
                </item>
    </channel>
</rss>