<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- DATA_FINGERPRINT:03b360fd855c9e97249f4da9a42ed116 -->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Internet Society Opportunities</title>
        <link>https://opportunities.internetsociety.org</link>
        <description>Latest opportunities to get involved with Internet Society initiatives</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://opportunities.internetsociety.org/data/opportunities.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
                    <title>Chapter Admin Funding</title>
                    <link>https://www.isocfoundation.org/grant-programme/chapter-admin-funding/</link>
                    <description>The Chapter Admin Funding program offers annual funding to support Internet Society chapters to manage their day-to-day activities and to maximize their effectiveness.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:17:18 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">80e02ad14c4ce39108bbc89b192d8bc5</guid>
                    <category>Opportunity</category>
                    <category>Funding &amp; Support</category>
                    <category>Global</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>Internet Governance Forum Events</title>
                    <link>https://www.isocfoundation.org/grant-programme/internet-governance-forum-events/</link>
                    <description>The Internet Society Foundation’s Internet Governance Forum (IGF) funding program supports the organization of United Nations (UN) IGF Secretariat-recognized National and Regional Initiatives (NRIs) and National and Regional Schools on Internet Governance. The purpose of the IGF is to encourage open, non-commercial, and inclusive multi-stakeholder dialogue on issues related to Internet governance. The goal of Schools on Internet Governance is to ensure that diverse actors have the skills to participate in Internet governance structures and shape the future of the Internet.</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:48:42 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">143755e045eb62c4910544515e1b3f1c</guid>
                    <category>Opportunity</category>
                    <category>Funding &amp; Support</category>
                    <category>Global</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>Beyond the Net Grant Program</title>
                    <link>https://www.isocfoundation.org/grant-programme/beyond-the-net-grant-program/</link>
                    <description>The Internet Society Foundation’s Beyond the Net Grant Program offers funding to support Internet Society Chapters to implement innovative projects that make a local impact by providing meaningful access to an open, trusted, and globally-connected Internet, as well as strengthening the Chapters’ presence in the surrounding community.</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:39:04 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c63ee1a927bcd523208651faf3a54824</guid>
                    <category>Opportunity</category>
                    <category>Funding &amp; Support</category>
                    <category>Global</category>
                </item>
<item>
                    <title>Join the Global Encryption Coalition</title>
                    <link>https://www.globalencryption.org/join/</link>
                    <description>Some governments and organizations are pushing to weaken encryption, which would create a dangerous precedent that compromises the security of billions of people worldwide. Actions in one country that undermine encryption threaten all of us.

With over 400 members distributed across 103 countries, the Global Encryption Coalition promotes and defends encryption in key countries and multilateral fora where it is under threat. It also supports efforts by companies to offer encrypted services to their users.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:11:29 GMT</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2a134b02ad2e360080e050cf5b37f0ae</guid>
                    <category>Opportunity</category>
                    <category>Ongoing Opportunities</category>
                    <category>Global</category>
                </item>
    </channel>
</rss>